# **KARTHIKEYAN.S**

**User Interface Designer** 

- +91 97897 00550
- karthickmscss@gmail.com
- 💡 Srinivasa Nagar,Coimbatore 36

# **OBJECTIVE**



I am a young and imaginative Web, Graphic and UI/UX Designer with 10+ years of experience in creating meaningful experiences through design. Persistence, Curiosity and an obsessive attention to detail define me and I am competent in all aspects of the design process. My only goal is to excel in the design world and to become one of the best design professionals.

I have some front end coding experience and enjoy working with devs to build ideas out. Able to take ideas from concept to wireframe to prototype to production.

I am currently seeking full time employment with an agency that has an environment encourages values, learning & growth, and effectively contributes to my personal development and the organizations growth.

# **EXPERIENCE**



June 2018 - Present

Dec 2017 - May 2018

Feb 2015 - Nov 2017

#### **Atom8 IT Solutions Pvt.Ltd**

Tidel Park, Coimbatore.

Sr.UI Designer

Designing Software User Interfaces, Designing UI for Web & Mobile Applications, Creating videos in Aftereffects, Creating mockups, Designing Web UI and front-end development, Designing Banners, Guiding other designers and front-end developers to make websites compatible with all browsers, Creating Logos, Designing Brochures, Letter Pads, Visiting Cards etc.,

### **Flocks Web Media Private Limited**

Tidel Park, Coimbatore.

**UI** Designer

Designed UI for Web & Mobile Applications, Created mockups, Designed Web UI and front-end development, Designed Banners, Created Logos, Designed Brochures, Letter Pads, Visiting Cards etc.,

#### **Nishta Nextgen Solutions**

Nanjundapuram Road, Coimbatore.

**UI** Designer

Designed Software User Interfaces, Designed UI for Web & Mobile Applications, Created mockups, Designed Web UI and front-end development, Designed Banners, Created Logos, Designed Brochures, Letter Pads, Visiting Cards etc.,

# **SKILLS**



- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Affinity Photo
- Affinity Designer
- After Effects
- Figma
- HTML/CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- iQuery

# **SPECIALIZED IN**



- UI/UX Design
- PSD to HTML Conversion
- Web Design

# **LANGUAGES**



- English
- Tamil

# **PERSONAL**



Date of birth	*
30/10/1988  Marital status	

# Religion

Hindu



#### **Accugile Technologies**

Vadavalli, Coimbatore.

#### **UI** Designer

Created mockups, Designed websites, UI Designs, front end development, Designed banners. Designed Canada, Australia, New Zealand, Auckland and US based websites. Created Logos, Designed Brochures, Letter Pads, Visiting Cards etc.

#### **Foresight Software Solutions**

Ganapathy, Coimbatore.

#### Web Designer

Started as a fresher, designed websites, front end development, Designed banners, Created Flash Intro pages for websites.

## **EDUCATION**



Jun 2013 - Jan 2015

May 2011 - Jan 2013

2006 - 2011 - CMS College

Marks 71%

#### **Higher Secondary**

**Master in Web Designing** 

2012 - Adoro Multimedia

2004 - 2006 - PSG Sarvajana Hr.Sec School

Marks 63%

Marks 90%

#### **High School**

1999 - 2004 - SRKV High School

Marks 92%

# **SOME SAMPLE PROJECTS ARE**

- www.taupotandemskydiving.com
- www.mongrov.com
- www.cobblawyer.us
- www.fourplay.co.nz
- www.citiesunited.org
- www.blackhorseoffroad.com
- www.learnprojectfinance.com
- www.technetics.com.au
- www.diwahealth.com
- www.skydivebayofislands.com
- www.robertshemin.com
- www.srisathyasai.org
- www.groov.one
- www.groov.app

# **INTERESTED IN**



- Photography
- Travelling
- Driving

# **PORTFOLIO**



www.karthick.tech

I hereby declare that information furnished above is true to best of my knowledge.

## Regards, **Karthikeyan**